Sensei, we'll quit this
lame school!
When all the adults around you
betray you?
What can you do?
I want her back that way.
The real Miyabi.
Murai-kun...
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Good morning, everyone.
This fall session,
let's make it great too!
Directed by
AKABANE HIROSHI
A Production of
KANSAI TEREBI & AVEC
Well everyone, welcome back
to the new school session.
- Um, excuse me...
- What is it?
Onizuka-sensei's not here yet.
I just got word.
The Education Board is coming
to observe
our Musashino Seirin Academy.
This would be the perfect chance
to show how outstanding
our academy is.
To see our earnestness
and our high ideals.
This is our chance to display that,
don't you think?
The head teacher's tension
is high, isn't it?
Losing the trust of the PTA must
have struck him hard.
Let's do our best, sir!
Now is the time to for us
as teachers to show
our zeal and enthusiasm!
Just because of one teacher,
our public morals have
been confused.
It is up to us to restore
this academy.
If the inspection goes well,
then we'll be able
to show who really
is the outstanding teachers.
It'll open the eyes
of the students!
They'll see who really
is thinking about them.
- That it's not that man, it is us!
- Yes!
Well then, the scheduling details
and everyone's roles
will be planned
by Nakamaru-sensei.
I understand.
"This is ridiculous!"
What the heck is that?
That was like Tesshî,
don't ya think?
- Nah!
- Nothing like him!
- "So Onizuka-sensei..."
- Nope.
'K then, how about Kotani!
"I do not approve of things
like miss contests."
- Quit it already!
- Then Nakamaru!
"Improper relations between
teachers
and students is not proper."
How's that!
No?
I got it, how about Yazawa?
"I love you."
Hey! Hey, hold on!
You know, now that the class
is finally back together,
- let's go karaoke!
- Sorry,
we're not in elementary
school anymore.
We're going to a Penicillin
concert.
Bye bye!
Penicillin? What's this Penicillin?
Oh?
So it's just you guys?
Oh well, wanna go somewhere?
Sorry, but I've got cram school.
- What's that?
- It is fall after all.
- We got exams pretty soon.
- Um, I'm busy.
Totally smooth with some
unreal babes!
- Total babe!
- No fair! Take me too!
How's that?!
MUSASHINO SEIRIN ACADEMY
You guys...
Don't you realize you're being
fooled by Onizuka?
Trust him and I guarantee you'll
get burned!
Or are you telling me,
you've become Onizuka's pets?
Miyabi...
I don't have a word
to say to you!
Nomura-san, why do you want
to quit school?
- I... I was scouted.
- Scouted?
The president from a famous
production company asked me if
I would enter their talent
development school.
That's great, Tomoko!
But you can't go to school
at the same time?
That talent school...
it's in Okinawa.
Okinawa?!
What should I do?
- You should do it.
- Think so?
Yeah! Didn't I say you're sure
to become an idol.
Hey, yeah, mention me
in your memoirs!
"In my life, there's someone
very important to me."
"My homeroom teacher
in high school..."
"No! Teacher in life.
He's Onizuka Eikichi-sensei."
Or something like that.
- That's not the issue here.
- What is?
Don't be ridiculous!
Do you think someone dizzy
like you can become an idol?
Of course not! Right?
You know,
we know you the best.
We only concerned for your
well-being.
If you quit school now,
you're sure to regret it.
- Oki...
- And Okinawa?
Don't be silly, how're you going
to get the money?
We won't give you a cent,
understand?
You should just graduate
from high school.
Find yourself a good husband,
and take over this store!
Listen to your parents.
This is because you let her take
those dance lessons!
Stupid! I let her do that because
for once she expressed
a desire to do something.
That's what I mean!
You're too easy!
She misinterpreted that
and now she's saying
- she want to be an idol!
- Excuse me,
would you listen to what
Tomoko-san has to say...
Please stay out of this!
This is a family matter!
This is the teachers' fault!
Because you put strange
ideas in her head.
Tomoko, you didn't say a thing!
- I'm sorry.
- Nomura-san,
maybe you should graduate
from high school after all.
If you really want
to become an idol,
then it won't be too
late then, will it?
What? How do you figure that?
Then what about her parents?
Like they said,
the world isn't kind.
That's what'll make it interesting
after she's an idol.
"The birth of a star, the legend
of Nomura Tomoko."
You just want to be on TV.
I just want Tomoko to become
an idol.
You just want to make money
off selling candid photos.
Why do you always talk bad
about people like that!
Never mind, please don't fight
because of me.
I'm going to think about it
some more.
You remembered.
There's no way I could forget.
The anniversary
of Takeshi's death.
Miyabi, think about how
he feels too...
Miyabi-chan!
What're you doing here, Dizzy?
There's something I had to talk
to you about.
No matter how much I ask,
- they'll never agree.
- What do you expect?
Don't you think that you winning
that special award was pure luck?
Well, maybe...
You're seventeen already.
Those who seriously want
to become idols
start taking lessons from when
they're small.
Even if you try hard from now,
do you think
someone like you can make it?
- I hadn't thought about that.
- And besides...
If you go to Okinawa,
you'll really be by yourself.
Even if you run into hard times,
no one is going to help you.
You'll have to do everything
yourself.
Do you think someone dizzy
like you can do it?
You're right.
For crying out loud,
you don't understand a thing!
I'm glad I talked to you!
I can count on you
after all, Miyabi-chan.
The members of the Board will
be led up to here.
Then, sir.
This is the directors office,
and that way is the staff room.
My, what wonderful facilities!
Something like that,
and then while
the members are admiring this...
Fuyutsuki-sensei will come out!
I am Fuyutsuki, I teach English.
We are so honored that you
have visited
our Musashino Seirin
Academy today.
Not at all. I'm so surprised
to find such a beauty here!
And as Fuyutsuki-sensei's smile
captures the hearts of the Board...
Sir!
Well then,
shall we go and see our teachers
and students in their wonderful
classes overflowing with energy?
This way, please.
And here is an outstanding class
in our academy
taught by Kotani-sensei.
The Way of Tea is the soul of Japan.
This exemplifies the beauty
and richness of what is held
in the heart of Japanese women.
I wish you to understand
the Tea Ceremony,
to understand this.
And so, for our academy's
students,
we wish to polish their femininity,
to ensure their future
as fine women, and to send them
into the world.
And now, next,
is the high level mathematics
of our academy.
Incidentally, this class'
Teshigawara-sensei's father...
Ministry of Education member.
Is a member of the Ministry
of Education.
This way.
And so, that is how this
is derived.
Hey, yo!
- What's he doing?
- I dunno!
Teshigawara's so into it!
You there! No slacking!
If you remain unprepared
like this,
your rivals will leave you behind!
- Don't you understand?
- What do you think?
This enthusiasm for teaching
to prepare them for success.
So this is how the new
elite is born.
Shall we continue?
That's perfect, sir!
By now, the members
of the Board will
unquestionably be impressed!
Excuse me...
Is this really a fair
representation?
What's that?
Well, rather than rehearsing
everything,
shouldn't we let them see
how we are normally?
So then, shall we have
the Education Board
- watch your class?
- Please, not that!
I'd be too self-conscious.
- Then please don't interfere!
- I'm sorry.
Sensei!
Working hard, aren't you,
Tomoko.
You know, Sensei...
Like Fuyutsuki-sensei said,
I've decided to wait until after
I graduate from high school.
Why?
Well, Miyabi-chan said
that's better too.
And besides, if I quit school,
I'll lose all my friends.
And thanks to you,
class now is so much fun!
I just have to think of being
happy in your class.
Tomoko.
Come.
I'm sorry, we're not ready yet...
- Excuse me.
- I'm home...
Hey! What are you doing?
What are you doing, Sensei?
- You're leaving home.
- What?
But wait, what about school?
- Your going to drop out.
- What?!
You want to become an idol
no matter what, right?
Then it doesn't matter if your
parents are against it,
or that you have to go far away
and be alone, right?
What about money?
I don't have any savings.
You can work, right?
If you're serious about this.
Don't you remember what you
said at the audition?
Didn't you say you wanted
to like yourself first?
Otherwise no one else
will like you.
If you keep this up, you'll be back
to where you started!
You have to value your
own feeling more.
You know those who say
to finish high school,
and who tell you other things.
You can't let them divert you!
If you're going to do it,
then become the best idol
in Japan ever!
Hold on! What's going on?
- Please explain...
- Pardon me.
I'm going...
Where are you going, Tomoko?
This is no joke!
This is like kidnapping!
Does a teacher have the right
to decide the future
of someone else's daughter?
What are you going
to do about this?
Return our daughter
immediately!
P-Please calm down! The head
teacher is asking about
- the situation right now.
- What's the meaning of this?
What kind of teacher forces
a student to leave home?
What's this?
Nomura Tomoko, as of today,
would like
to quit Musashino
Seirin Academy.
What in heaven's name
are you saying?
To force students who
were expelled
from school to come back.
And now to force a student who
want to come to school to leave?
No, see, Tomoko wrote out
a request here to drop out.
Just because you got the student
of your class to return,
don't get carried away.
Even if you've fooled the children,
you won't fool us teachers!
- What's that got to do with it?
- In any case,
the Education Board will
be inspecting,
and this is not the time for this!
Until the inspection is over,
don't cause any problems!
So, don't do a single thing!
Don't do anything!
Don't say a word,
don't even breathe!
Don't lay a finger
on my daughter!
- Your daughter?
- Uh...
In any case...
stay out of my way!
Otherwise, I'll get you thrown out
of this academy!
I believe in her.
I believe this is best for Tomoko.
Wait! You can't just...
What's going on?
She isn't going to drop out,
is she?
No, please don't worry.
We cannot accept her request
to drop out.
We will take responsibility
for your daughter
and return her home.
You're here, aren't you,
Nomura-san?
- Oh, Sensei!
- You're here!
Youch!
Why don't you clean up a little!
Why should I?
Nomura-san, your parents are
worried about you.
You may have understood
everything up to now,
but it's different this time.
This is too callous!
To just have her leave home,
and to just put in a request
to drop out.
I figured rather than have
Tomoko be all worried,
that this was better.
Don't you think it's valuable
that she worries too?
Do you have the right
to take that away?
That's not what I intended.
That's what I mean by a lack
of common sense!
Do you think she can go
to Okinawa like this,
without her parents
forgiving her?
But it's Tomoko's life.
Then it's okay if she can
never return home?
Will it be alright to live her
whole life after fighting
- with her parents?
- But...
She's the one who's
going to suffer!
- But you don't understand!
- Please stop!
Onizuka-sensei did this for me.
Nomura-san, that may be so...
Oh, Eikichi! I've finally
found you!
You wouldn't tell me
where you live.
Do you know how
I suffered to find you?
- What are you doing?
- I had a fight with my dad.
- And I left home.
- What?
I know it's asking a lot.
But please, thank you!
What are you... What?!
You don't mean you're going
to stay here?
Of course!
Because you're my prince
on his white horse!
Oh geeze, don't just go off
and decide that for yourself!
Oh?
You're the teacher
from last time?
Oh problems? How terrible!
Oh, I'll make some tea!
No thank you. We're done with
our business here.
- Let's go, Nomura-san.
- What? Oh, okay.
Um, Fuyutsuki-sensei?
Don't worry, I will take her
to my place.
So please enjoy yourselves.
- There's no need to...
- Excuse us!
What now...
- Make yourself at home.
- Thanks.
- Is orange juice okay?
- Yes.
Wow.
This really feels like
a grown-up's room.
- You like him too!
- You too?
- He's great, isn't he?
- He is, isn't he?
Oh!
Gâko!
It's been a long time!
How've you been?
Good! How about you,
Tomo-chan?
Is it okay if you don't
go back home?
Is it really okay, like this?
I don't know, Gâko.
What should I do, Sensei?
That's right...
Sensei, what did you want
to become when you
- were my age?
- Me?
Well...
- Don't tell anyone.
- I promise!
You see...
- A stewardess!
- Really?
You can go all over the world.
I thought that was great,
and I wanted to do that
from when I was a kid.
So, when did you decide
to become a teacher?
Why did you decide
Well, that...
Oh sorry, excuse me.
- Yes?
- Hello, Azusa, it's me!
- Oh, what's up?
- I heard just now,
there's going to be a vacancy
at our company soon!
And the exam's coming up soon.
Azusa, you should take it!
You don't like being
a teacher, right?
- Then you should do it!
- You're right.
Then I'll send you
the documents!
You should be thankful you
have such good friends!
Thanks! Bye.
You're good!
Would you teach me?
One, two... One, two...
Something like that...
Your dad must be worried
about you!
You shouldn't leave home!
You should talk, you put up
one of your own students!
- That was different...
- Here, thanks for waiting.
Let's eat.
Hurry up.
Ittadakimasu.
Hey, Eikichi!
You've got a visitor.
- Who?
- Yohoo!
Yohoo?
What are you doing here,
Yoshiko?
Mama, what are you
doing here?!
Your mom?
Um, your daughter showed up
by herself.
- I've also left home.
- Oh, did you and dad fight too?
- Can I sit here?
- No, that's Eikichi-san's.
You see, he's saying that it's all
my fault you left home.
But it really was all
Papa's fault, right?
He doesn't get, does he?
I'm starved.
Is there enough for me?
Oh, yes! I made plenty.
Excuse me!
- But this is my place.
- I'm so sorry, Eikichi-san.
Sorry we will be imposing.
Thank you very much.
- No, but...
- Here Mama, thanks for waiting!
- It's pretty good.
- It's yummy, you know!
You're the man!
All of a sudden,
you're living with women.
Hello, this is Uchiyamada.
I just wanted to ask...
Is my wife and daughter
at your place?
Oh, I see.
No, that's fine.
No, no! It's nothing important.
Thank you.
They wouldn't...
They wouldn't be at Onizuka's...
There's no way!
No matter what...
They would never...
What's that? Tomoko's gone?!
When I woke up, I found this.
Just where'd Tomoko go?
It looks like she hasn't
returned home either.
How could you be so
irresponsible!
What?! It's because you brought
that strange girl in.
I told you, she isn't
anyone special.
Really?
In any case, it was originally
your fault anyway!
Because you do whatever without
thinking of the consequences.
It's because she keeps thinking
about the consequences
that she keeps getting stuck
halfway and never does anything!
So do you have the confidence
to say that in ten to twenty years,
- it was good for her?
- Nope.
Then will you take responsibility?
- Then... maybe...
Like your pattern up to now,
do you have something great
planned to solve this?
- No!
- You're unbelievable!
Of course her parents
would be angry!
Do you always have
to know your future?
Can you not do anything unless
your future is guaranteed?
What's the fun in that?
Didn't you say so yourself?
You end up just waiting for your
prince on a white horse
to come for you.
Didn't you say so yourself?
You didn't want Tomoko
to live her life like that?
That the most important
thing for a woman
is to have more confidence
in herself?
What are you doing?
This brings back memories!
We played here a lot, didn't we?
Hey! Remember when
I fell off of that?
Didn't you want to talk
about something?
Oh, sorry.
Right now, I'm stuck.
I submitted my request
to drop out,
but if my father and mother
don't agree to it,
the head teacher won't
approve it.
I don't know what
to do anymore!
My father and mother are totally
against me going to Okinawa.
But Onizuka-sensei says
that I have to go.
They're all saying this
for my benefit,
so I want everyone
to be happy.
But there's no way
I can do that.
Umm, so...
- Um, well...
- Geeze, you drive me nuts.
What do you want to do?
Miyabi-chan, if you told me
to go and do my best,
then I think I could get up
the courage to go to Okinawa.
What are you talking about?
There's no way
I can tell you that.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, then...
Will you listen to this one thing
I have to say?
What is it?
Please stop your bullying
and come back to school.
Miyabi-chan, you're a lot
smarter than me,
so you should know by now,
that Onizuka-sensei
is different from all the other
teachers before.
That you can trust him.
Please, Miyabi-chan.
You know, you don't have time
to worry about that.
If you've got time for that,
then do something
about yourself!
Well then, shall we go
and see our teachers
and students in their wonderful
classes overflowing with energy?
This way please.
Oh my, thank you for coming.
You must be hot.
Please, have some of our
excellent milk.
- Oh, well!
- Please!
Thank you!
Oh, yes...
Where is the director today?
The director...
Um, well, the director...
What's happened to her,
Nakamaru-sensei?
Uh, err...
Oh! Well, she said something
about not feeling too well today.
Please, everyone.
Shall we?
Oh, you know, she said
something about
class 2-4 being very enjoyable.
- Right, sir?
- Is that so?
Yes, um.
Let's get going.
Alright, take your seats!
- What are you doing, Tomoko?
- What?
You aren't a student in this
class anymore.
But the head teacher hasn't...
It doesn't matter what
Uchiyamada says.
Get out.
What are you doing, hurry up.
I told you get out!
Don't you feel sorry
for her, Onitchi?
It isn't official that she's
dropped out, right?
- Think about how Tomoko feels!
- You guys stay out of this.
Tomoko, come on,
hurry up.
This isn't the place
for you anymore!
Everyone...
Thank you for everything...
Alright, let's make today
another great day!
Nomura-san.
What's wrong?
Onizuka-sensei told me
that I'm no longer
a student of class 2-4.
I see.
What should we do?
I think you know already.
Yes...
Here!
Sensei...
Nomura-san,
I'm thinking of taking
the stewardess entrance exam.
Then are you going to quit
being a teacher?
I don't know.
But so I won't regret it,
I'm going to do what I can.
I'm learning from your example
and not thinking
about the consequences.
- Good luck, Sensei!
- Thanks!
Isn't this the wrong way around?
I'm the one being cheered on.
OKINAWA, 3:55 P.M.
- Now then, let's move on.
- This way please.
Oh! Isn't this that class 2-4?
I'd love to take a look.
Yes, well, there isn't really
much to see.
We need to keep
to the schedule.
Don't be so dull!
What is this?
Is that Onizuka up to
something again?
Well you see, this man, he isn't
really well suited to be a teacher...
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO ATTEND
OR WATCH CLASS,
WE'VE GONE TO THE AIRPORT
Thank you very much!
Hang in there, Nomura-san!
You too, Sensei, hang in there!
Sensei!
Come on!
Even if you quit school,
we're still your friends, Tomoko.
Thanks, everyone!
Tomoko, become Japan's
number one idol!
Thank you, Sensei.
- Tomoko!
Dad! Mom!
Tomoko...
Go do your best!
Don't let those other girls
get to you!
But why?
Yesterday, Miyabi-chan came by.
She lectured us, you know.
Miyabi-chan said,
that Tomoko was much more
mature than herself.
So, she was sure you'd be fine.
- Tomoko, take care!
- Hey, no need to cry!
- Write, okay?
- Do your best!
Thank you, everyone.
I... I...
I want you all to get along
with Miyabi-chan.
Miyabi-chan may be putting
on a strong face.
But actually she's lonely.
She's lost right now.
She's suffering.
That's why, please...
Sensei, please take care of her.
Well then, I'm going.
- Do your best, Tomoko!
- Do your best!
Don't give up!
You guys...
are great!
Just like in a school drama!
You're the best!
Do your best, Tomoko!
Tomoko, good luck!
Onizuka...
He was thinking only of Tomoko
and made her quit school.
Everyone up to now would just
say it was for our sakes.
But they'd only be thinking
of their own situation.
Onizuka doesn't care about
his own position at all!
Give it up already, Miyabi.
Stop this bullying of yours!
Otherwise, I don't know you!
You know, this isn't
the you that I like!
- Onitchi, let's go.
- Let's go.
Hey!
- Check it out! He's crying!
- Hey, shaddap!
It's karaoke tonight for sure!
- Here.
- Thanks.
Are you okay?
Takeshi?!
What were you doing,
on the day of the inspection!
Seeing their friend off was
an important extracurricular class.
What?!
Excuse us.
It seems we weren't thinking
of how Tomoko felt,
we were only thinking
of ourselves.
We're sorry for the trouble.
Please accept her request
to drop out.
- Please.
- Oh, please, can I?
- Sir, do you have a minute?
- Can you wait till later.
We've found a way
to get rid of Onizuka!
It's rather simple.
What is it?
What?! Are you serious?!
Oh man, give me a break!
2016-07